<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Musings on Aaron Machuca</title>
    <link>https://aaronmachuca.com/musings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Musings on Aaron Machuca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 11:43:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://aaronmachuca.com/musings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Skating Through a New Lens</title>
      <link>https://aaronmachuca.com/musings/skating-through-a-new-lens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 11:43:22 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aaronmachuca.com/musings/skating-through-a-new-lens/</guid>
      <description>Photo(s) by Ruijie Shao Having been born and raised in the slums of eastern Los Angeles, I used to hold a strong disdain for urban society and the lifestyle imposed upon its residents (myself included). This sentiment is of course no secret those who have held a conversation with me for more than a day, but is something I regularly felt compelled to mention because I failed to understand the appeal of big cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Art and Poetry</title>
      <link>https://aaronmachuca.com/musings/on-art-and-poetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 11:42:25 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aaronmachuca.com/musings/on-art-and-poetry/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The mapping of the human genome was completed early this century. As a result, the evolutionary log of the human race lay open to us. We started with genetic engineering, and in the end, we succeeded in digitizing life itself. But there are things not covered by genetic information. Human memories, ideas. Culture. History. Genes don&amp;rsquo;t contain any record of human history. Is it something that should not be passed on?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drop the Topster</title>
      <link>https://aaronmachuca.com/musings/drop-the-topster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 18:14:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aaronmachuca.com/musings/drop-the-topster/</guid>
      <description>Who could&amp;rsquo;ve possibly seen this one coming. With apologies to all my friends who had to endure my constantly updated music charts for years on end. But for real this time, here are my current top 42 albums. Music has always played an interesting role in my life as it&amp;rsquo;s always been the one artistic medium I have never had the desire to engage with beyond dabbling, but ACTUALLY dabbling, in some instruments here and there.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
